[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Supermans secret identity, and where does he work?", "correct_answer": "Clark Kent, Daily Planet", "incorrect_answers": ["Mark Kennedy, Daily Planet", "Mark Kennedy, Daily Report", "Clark Kent, Daily Report"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The AAT appears in two Star Wars movies.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which central European countrys all pre-1989 neighbors do not exist any more? The country is now bordered by 7 states.", "correct_answer": "Poland", "incorrect_answers": ["Austria", "Hungary", "Romania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What sea creature has 3 hearts and 8 tentacles?", "correct_answer": "octopus", "incorrect_answers": ["sea worm", "crab", "squid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What important advantage does algal fuel possess?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It is relatively environmentally harmless.", "It is biodegradable.", "It produces much more energy than second-generation biofuel crops."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average height a potato plant can reach?", "correct_answer": "60 centimeters", "incorrect_answers": ["40 centimeters", "20 centimeters", "80 centimeter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Windows NT is a family of operating systems produced by Microsoft. What does NT stand for?", "correct_answer": "New Technology", "incorrect_answers": ["Network Technology", "Network Terminal", "Networking and Troubleshooting"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How can jaguars be described in terms of social activity?", "correct_answer": "Solitary", "incorrect_answers": ["Sociable", "Group animals", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Part of the Southeast Ridge Route for climbing Mt. Everest is the Lhotse Face in which Camp III is established. There are 14 peaks over 8,000 meters. Where does Lhotse rank?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "8", "13"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where are the gliding membranes of the Draco lizard species positioned?", "correct_answer": "On their elongated ribs", "incorrect_answers": ["Between their fingers and toes", "Between its front and hind legs", "They do not have a gliding membrane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first name of Napoleons Hispanic friend in the movie Napoleon Dynamite?", "correct_answer": "Pedro", "incorrect_answers": ["Jesus", "Paco", "Jose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Triceratops fossils have been found on three continents.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]